climber.com 2018-12-30

# Climber.com - Connect to Recruiters, Career Social Networking, Career and Job Search

At Climber.com, we value your privacy. This privacy policy was created to provide a clear explanation of how your personal information and privacy will be safeguarded.

Climber.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

Since many of the financial services that we offer do require the collection of sensitive information, we want you to understand what types of information we are collecting and what may happen to that information.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please email us at: privacy@climber.com

## 1\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

Information is collected from our users at several different points during your visit to Climber.com.

Qualification – One of the services Climber.com offers is access to a low-interest rate student loan consolidation program. A user must complete the qualification page in order to apply for Student Loan Consolidation. During Qualification, a user is required to provide certain pieces of information, such as name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, Social Security Number (optional) and to answer three qualifying questions. This information is used to determine your eligibility for a student consolidation loan and may be provided to the lender and/or servicer who completes your consolidation. If it is determined that you are not eligible for our consolidation program, we may share your information with other consolidation companies that offer consolidation programs more suited to your needs.

Optional Information - At various other points during your visit to Climber.com, you may be asked to provide information about yourself. For example, you may wish to participate in a survey or a contest. Participation in surveys or contests or the use of other services which require the input of additional information is completely voluntary on your part, and you have the choice about whether to disclose the information necessary to use these features of our site.

Passive Collection of Information - In addition to the information which you actively provide to Climber.com by methods described above, Climber.com collects information about how you interact with our site. Climber.com collects passive information for purposes such as testing and improving a user's experience at the site and the compilation of broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information for internal purposes and for disclosure to third parties such as advertisers and content partners. The types of passive information collected by this site include, without limitation, your IP address, which type of browser you are using, where you go on our site, and how long you stay on any part of our site. Passive information does not identify you to Climber.com by name, and Climber.com does not link your IP address to your personally identifiable information.

Collection of Information from Children - Climber.com abides by federal law and the "Youth Privacy" guidelines set up by the Federal Trade Commission. Therefore, Climber.com will not knowingly collect any personal information from or allow the registration of young people under the age of 13.

## 2\. USE OF INFORMATION

Incentivized Signups 

Climber.com may use your information you have provided in order to customize our site to your interests and enhance your overall experience at our site. Climber.com tries to recognize you using various methods, including having you log in with your e-mail address and your password. Once Climber.com recognizes you, pages, advertisements and other content is customized for you so that you can see what interests you the most. In addition, as described above, Climber.com utilizes passive information to learn more about how you interact with our site. This passive information may be combined with your other information for purposes such as testing and improving your experience at our site and the compilation of broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information for internal purposes and for disclosure to third parties such as advertisers and content partners. This aggregate passive information does not contain any personal information which can identify any individual user.

Contacting You by E-Mail - Climber.com may use your contact information periodically in order to send you e-mail regarding updates at the Climber.com site, such as new Climber.com opportunities and additional listings which may be of interest to you. The frequency of these messages will vary depending upon your demographic interests. In addition, we may send you free informational newsletters or notices relating to topics which may be of special interest to you, including financial aid and financial services. If you voluntarily opt-in to receive offers from specific partners or third parties, you may also receive promotional e-mails from those partners. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to opt-out of receiving newsletters and/or commercial e-mails whenever such messages are sent by Climber.com. E-mail messages from third parties are not governed by the opt-out provisions of this Privacy Policy, but all such third parties are strongly encouraged to include opt-out procedures in their messages to you.

Contacting You by Phone - Climber.com may use your contact information periodically contact you regarding services, updates and opportunities. These may be done using auto-dialing technology. Climber.com may use third-party platforms to conduct these calls and leave voice mail messages.

## 3\. SHARING OF INFORMATION

Climber.com will not knowingly sell, share, rent or otherwise transfer your information other than in accordance with the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy.

General Policy - Climber.com understands how important your personal information is to you. Therefore, Climber.com does not share any information that can be tied to you without your permission. If you give your permission to allow third parties to contact you, personal information about you (such as your contact information and other information collected during your visit to Climber.com) may be shared with data aggregators, marketers (possibly in the form of list rental), and other organizations. Regardless of your decision regarding the sharing of your personal information, we may share broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information with our business partners. This aggregate information does not contain any personal information which can identify any individual user.

Pre-Population - Occasionally Climber.com may present opportunities to complete forms or applications for various financial services both on our site and on our Partner's Web sites. Sometimes, when these forms are presented, Climber.com will pre-populate the forms, both on Climber.com and on our Partner Web sites with some of your personal information, such as name, mailing address, phone-number, date of birth or other pieces of information. Even though, this information is pre-populated on a Partner's Web site, that specific Partner will not have access to or store your personal information unless you choose to complete the form and submit the information. If you decide not to complete the form, the specific Partner will not have seen or recorded your personal information.

Third Party Service Providers - From time to time, Climber.com may decide that it is more efficient to use third parties to perform specific services, such as sending newsletters to Climber.com's users. If we use a third party to provide specific services (such as sending newsletters to our users on our behalf), then information (such as contact information, applicable demographic information, or account information) may be shared with that party to the extent necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third party service providers are only allowed to use personally identifiable information for the purpose of providing the specific services requested by Climber.com. The third party services covered by this paragraph do not include links to third party sites found on our site, which are governed by a more specific provision (Links to Other Sites) below.

Disclosure to Law Enforcement and Similar Disclosures - While Climber.com strives to protect the personal information of our users, Climber.com will release personal information if required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary or appropriate.

## 4\. USE OF COOKIES & LOG FILES

When you visit our site, a cookie (a very small text file) is placed on your machine (if it is accepted), this to provide you with a personalised experience and to assist in the collection of the site visitation statistics. You may refuse the cookie, if you wish. To do so, you will need to check your browser settings.

Climber.com collects certain information about your computer hardware and software, this includes (however is not limited to):

  * Your IP Address
  * Browser Type
  * Operating System
  * Access Times
  * Referring Web Site Addresses

This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of Climber.com's web sites. Cookies are also used in connection with the membership of our site. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies, you will be able to view the majority of our site. We retain the right to use cookies for advertising purposes.

## 5\. THIRD PARTY COOKIES

We, or a data provider we have engaged, may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads, content or services.   No personally identifiable information is on, or is connected to these cookies.  The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to the registration data you have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to http://www.privacychoice.org/companies or http://www.aboutads.info/choices.

## 6\. CORRECTING, UPDATING OR REMOVING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

If your personal information is incorrect, changes or if you no longer wish to receive information from Climber.com, we will endeavour to correct, update or remove your information as quickly as possible. This can be done by e-mailing customerservice@climber.com or calling our customer service phone number 1-800-684-9766.

## 7\. MOBILE ANALYTICS

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality and performance of our mobile software on your phone. This software may collect, store and use information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. This software may share information it collects with other third parties as part of providing the analytics services and to comply with applicable laws.

## 8\. LINKS TO OTHER SITES

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

## 9\. OTHER PROVISIONS

Acceptance of Terms/Changes to Privacy Policy - Your use of this site indicates an acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy. Climber.com reserves the right to update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. 

Disclaimer - Climber.com provides information on many topics. Some of this information is created by Climber.com, and some of it is created by third parties. While our site strives to provide accurate expert advice, commentary and other information, Climber.com does not make any warranty regarding the accuracy, reliability or use of any information provided on this site, including calculators and other tools.

Other - In the event that Climber.com sells, assigns or transfers some or all of its business to a successor or acquirer, Climber.com may sell, assign or transfer all of your information, regardless of your opt status, to such successor or acquirer.

Links to Other Sites - This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Climber.com does not exercise control over the information, products, services or policies of third party companies accessible through our site. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every third party site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the information collected by this site.

Changes to Privacy Policy - Climber.com reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy at any point. Users will always have access to our current Privacy Policy by visiting www.Climber.com.
